yogaworks.com 2017-07-19

# Privacy Policy | YogaWorks

## AST UPDATED: JULY 2014

## OVERVIEW

At Yoga Works, Inc. (“YogaWorks”) your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell, rent, or share your personal information to or with third parties without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

## SCOPE OF POLICY

This privacy policy applies to our websites, blogs, mobile sites, and applications, including the www.myyogaworks.com website, the www.yogaworksblog.com website, the www.yogaworks.com website, and the mobile versions thereof. It does not apply to other companies’ or organizations’ web sites to which we link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how your personal information is treated by such third parties.

## INFORMATION GATHERED FROM ALL VISITORS

Aggregate Data:  
We gather certain generic information with respect to all visitors’ use of our web sites, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web sites that they favor. We only use this type of data in aggregate, that is we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our web sites to make your experience easier and more enjoyable. We may also provide statistical “ratings” about how our customers collectively use our web sites to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our sites. We use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.

Cookies:  
We use a technology nicknamed “cookies” on our web sites. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies may be set upon your browser during site visits to save your site customization preferences and to save your passwords so you do not have to re-enter passwords upon each site visit. Cookies help you navigate our web sites, and help us customize our web sites to provide personal service. We also use cookies to track user sessions and to gather site usage statistics.

IP Addresses:  
We collect and analyze traffic on our web sites by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

Applications:  
We collect generic information through applications, including mobile applications or widgets.

Surveys:  
From time to time, we may conduct surveys or solicit your feedback. These surveys are used to gather information to improve our sites and provide a more meaningful experience for our users. We may also use the information to alert you to offers and products in which you have expressed an interest.

## COMMUNICATIONS

YogaWorks reserves the right to communicate with you from time to time about important administrative, policy, legal, credit card, and billing matters, which will affect your use of our myyogaworks.com web site, including any alleged violations of the applicable web site Terms and Conditions. If you are an account holder, you will automatically receive the following e-mails unless you choose to not receive them by going to the “Account Login” page or by following the instructions at the bottom of each e-mail message on how to unsubscribe: (i) to contact you for feedback and surveys; or (ii) to send you relevant company or service-related information.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION GATHERED FROM USERS

If you elect to open a user account on our myyogaworks.com web site, you will be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card, debit card or account number, expiration date, and billing address (this required information is subject to change from time to time).

If you elect to open a member account on our yogaworks.com web site, you will be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, e-mail address, address, phone number and date of birth (this required information is subject to change from time to time).

If you elect to post a comment or leave a reply on the myyogaworksblog.com web site, you will be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name and e-mail address (this required information is subject to change from time to time).

There may also be opportunities for you to provide us with additional information regarding your preferences and interests, and we may also use this information to make recommendations to you regarding specific teachers and classes. This information, however, is not required and is completely optional on your part.

In general, we will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided, such as communications, billing and processing your account. We may also track your use of our myyogaworks.com web site to determine which classes you participate in so that we can make recommendations to you regarding specific teachers and classes. We also use such information to deliver to you information about YogaWorks and our promotions. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings from us by following the instructions set forth below. We also use information for trend analysis, pattern detection, and site administration. Your personal information may also be disclosed to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, reorganization assignment, transfer or disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock.

Your information may be disclosed by you, on blogs, message boards and other services to which you are able to post information and materials. You should be aware that any information you disclose through these services will become public information, and may be available to the general public.

Your information provided to us on our myyogaworksblog.com web site may also be disclosed to your friends associated with your social media accounts, other users, and to your social media account provider, in connection with your social sharing activities, such as if you connect your social media accounts to your use of our myyogaworksblog.com web site. You authorize us to share your information with your social media account provider by connecting your use of our myyogaworksblog.com web site to your social media accounts.

## DISCLOSURE EXCEPTIONS

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law: (i) to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; (ii) to protect YogaWorks’ rights and property; (iii) to investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages; (iv) to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web sites and/or the YogaWorks service; or (v) during emergencies, such as when we believe someone’s physical safety is at risk.

## YOUR CONTROL OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Every communication YogaWorks sends you will contain a clearly worded “Opt-Out” or “Unsubscribe” link allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Permission changes will be honored as soon as possible after receipt. Please allow five to seven days for processing. Permission changes will however not affect any information that you provided to us.

Editing Your Profile:  
If you are a registered user of our myyogaworks.com web site or yogaworks.com website, you have the ability to review, correct, and change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Simply sign into the site and click the “My Account” link on the header of every page. There, you can change your personal and address information, sign-in, and e-mail preferences.

## OTHER MATTERS

Privacy of Children- COPPA Compliance:  
Our sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. We assume user accounts on our myyogaworks.com web site are opened by adults. We operate our sites in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.

California Residents:  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to web sites who are residents of California to request information regarding the web site owner’s disclosure of their personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. It is our policy not to disclose your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

Changes to the Privacy Policy:  
Modifications to our privacy policy will be reflected first within this area of this web site. If there is a material change in our privacy policy, we will indicate on this site that our policy has changed and provide a link to the new/revised privacy statement.

California Do Not Track Notice Disclosures:  
We do not track our users and visitors over time and across third party web sites to provide targeted advertising. Consequently, we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Other third party web sites may keep track of your browsing activities when they provide you with content, which enables them to customize what they present to you on their web sites.

## ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

Your use of our web sites, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy policy and the applicable web site Terms and Conditions. BY USING OUR WEB SITES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE WEB SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the effective date at the top of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our web sites following posting of the updated privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

Questions or Comments:  
If you have any questions or comments about this Agreement or the Site, please contact YogaWorks at (310) 664-6470.
